VERSION 0.0.0.3
Compatibility Fixes
	- Added some extra DPI functions to support new (4.4.3) versions of
	  qBittorrent.
General Improvements
	- Add NtRaiseHardError hook in order to provide more useful error
	  messages.

VERSION 0.0.0.2
General Improvements
	- Improved behavior when launching console applications through CMD or
	  PowerShell. Input and output are no longer interspersed.
	- Small code improvements and performance improvements.

VERSION 0.0.0.1
	Initial version. Basic functionality is working.